

A Videographer with entry-level experience, specializing in camera operations, film shoots, video editing, and Adobe After Effects, A strong history of planning shoots, coordinating with videography teams, and recording live events for clients.

123 Your Street, Philadelphia, PA 12345 antho nym i ller@ exa mp le.com (123) 456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

VIDEOGRAPHER

South Philly Wedding Video Pros., Philadelphia, PA I May 2021 - Present

- ♦ Execute 20+ video shoot projects valued at \$3K-\$5K for weddings, interface with clients to establish camera angles for the wedding ceremony and reception
- Conduct editing of wedding videos in Adobe After Effects and Final Cut Pro and created five-minute recap videos of the event from four hours of video content
- · Plan lighting and mic placement to deliver high-quality sound and video assets
- · Manage the setup and breakdown of cameras, boom mics, and lighting equipment

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

VIDEO PROJECTS

Temple University, Philadelphia, PA | September 2019 - May 2021

- ◆ Managed a video project to film art displays from students in Temple's art program, which included coordinating lighting, planning shoots, and conducting interviews with students on art pieces within the gallery
- Filmed interviews with students within the Jewish community to create a short documentary on the experience of Jewish students on Temple's campus

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS (B.A.) FILM

Temple University, Philadelphia, P September 2016 - May 2021

KEY SKILLS

- ♦ Videography
- ◆ Camera Operation
- ♦ Video Editing
- ♦ Audio Mixing
- Lighting

CERTIFICATIONS

♦ Apple Certified Pro, Final Cut Pro X, May 2021